Turn on
The ignition
Turn on,
turn on...
Start it up,
turn it on
Start it up, turn it on
We can ride this storm
A grip of hope in our hands
For the coming dawn
Up to our necks in complexities
Causing us to pause
As we collect our thoughts
So don't blink if you wanna
come cross the border
Take a look around
or come test the water
We won't stop
'till we see the morning
So welcome to the quiet
before the storm hits
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Take it up a notch
Comatose, Half-hearted
Room temperature's fine
Sleep walking, no dream
is even filling our minds
Earth quaking,
We be shaking like a wake up bomb
This ain't no trouble overseas
No Vietnam
So don't blink if you wanna
come cross the border
Take a look around
or come test the water
We won't stop
'till we see the morning
So welcome to the quiet
before the storm hits
Take it up a notch
Houston!
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Sleep walking
I'm sleep walking
I'm still talking
Come spark the parts in me
that all but died
Jump start my heart
and wake the sleeper inside
Hold up the flag 'cause it's ride or die
Hold up the flag 'cause it's ride or die!
Turn on the ignition,
turn on...
Come on!
Turn on the ignition,
turn on...
Here we go again!
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on, turn on the ignition
Everybody
Come on, come on
and turn on the ignition
Turn on the ignition,
turn on...
Come on!
Turn on the ignition,
turn on
Turn on the ignition
Come spark the parts in me
that all but died
Turn on the ignition
Jump start my heart
and wake the sleeper inside
Just lean with us
Slackin' off like a bum,
I'm feelin' ho hum
I'm feelin' luke warm
like the water in my tub
Started out and we was hot,
looked up and now we're not
We had that fire like we was boilin' in an pot
So let me hear you say
Whoopsi-daisy (3x)
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire, I'm feenin' for a flicker
Then we'll fan the flame up into something bigger
Started out and we was hot
looked up and now we're not
We gonna catch a fire, catch a fire for God
Come now!
Whoopsi-daisy, whoopsi-daisy, whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire, takin' it from warm to hot (we go)
Fire, gotta give it all we got (we go)
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy, whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Nirva D., what you got for me?
What you got for Houston, Texas?
Spark to a flame
I'm flippin' up my game
I caught the fire
and I'll never be the same
So unexplainable
I can't contain it, son
And my retaining it would only be a shame
So let me hear you say
Whoopsi-daisy
(Whoopsi-daisy)
Come, we gonna catch that
Heat,
Like the Kingston concrete
There ain't no stoppin' the fire
(Shonlock)
We're straight breakin' ground
There ain't no cooling this thing down
I'll put it up and keep'n
it krunk as we know how
Hear me now people
Whoopsi-daisy, whoopsi-daisy, whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy, whoopsi-daisy
Fire, takin' it from warm to hot (we go)
Fire, gotta give it all we got (we go)
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy, whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire
Fire!
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy, whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
What's goin' on Texas?
Are you ready to
catch a fire tonight?
Hoo-a-hoo, down down down
Here come the boy from Tennessee town
Hoo-a-oo, --?--
Here come the boy boy boy...
--?--
I confess it with my mouth just to make it flow
Catch a fire
Let it burn --?--
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy, whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Whoopsi-daisy
Call me crazy
Come, we gonna catch that
This goes out to anyone listen
Out the stereo system
Ladies and gentleman
DJ Maj
I've been around the way
I've been around the block
I got the keys to the city
if the gates are locked
And a freak like me
ain't bout to stop
I got a hand full of dreams
and a heart full of God
Everywhere we go they wonder where we're from
Well its diverse city ya'll welcome to come
It sits high in the hills you can see it for days
And even if you can't you can hear our praise
We go ...
'Cause we're boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out the stereo system
Here to rep the most high with this one
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out the stereo system
'Cause we rock for sure in stereo
Boomin' out your stereo
If you're looking to slide,
come slide with us
And if you're looking for a
ride, it's a big old bus
We got black folk, white folk
and Middle East
Mexican, Filipino - Jesus Freaks
Got a Haitian Princess, an Aussie Mate
East Coast, Midwest
to left side of the states
And when the bus rolls,
it's out the dirty south
Tennessee and we keepin' it
good and loud we go
'Cause we're boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out the stereo system
Here to rep the most high with this one
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out the stereo system
Boomin' out your stereo
Welcome to the Portable Sounds --?--
I got portable sounds to lift me up
Portable sounds to take me higher
Portable sounds to lift me up
So don't even try to get in my head
I got portable sounds to lift me up
Portable sounds to take me higher
Portable sounds to lift me up
So don't even try to get in my head, take it on
We got portable sounds to lift us
Portable sounds to take us higher
Portable sounds to lift us up
Portable sounds to take us higher (Shounlcok)
Shonlock!
--?--
Boomin' out the stereo
Stereo!
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Here to rep the most high with this one
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out your stereo
We're boomin' the truth
out the speakers, yo!
Bommin' out the stereo