Just lean with us
Slackin' off like a bum,
I'm feelin' ho hum
I'm feelin' luke warm
like the water in my tub
Started out and we was hot,
looked up and now we're not
We had that fire
like we was boilin' in an pot
So let me hear you say
Whoopsi-daisy (3x)
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire, I'm feenin' for a flicker
Then we'll fan the flame up
into something bigger
Started out and we was hot
looked up and now we're not
We gonna catch a fire,
catch a fire for God
- Come now!
- Whoopsi-daisy (3x)
Come, we gonna catch that
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire, takin' it from warm to hot (we go)
Fire, gotta give it all we got (we go)
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Nirva D., what you got for me?
What you got for Houston, Texas?
Spark to a flame
I'm flippin' up my game
I caught the fire
and I'll never be the same
So unexplainable
I can't contain it, son
And my retaining it would only be a shame
So let me hear you say
- Whoopsi-daisy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Heat, like the Kingston concrete
There ain't no stoppin' the fire
We're straight breakin' ground
There ain't no cooling this thing down
I'll put it up and keep'n
it krunk as we know how
Hear me now people
Whoopsi-daisy, whoopsi-daisy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire, takin' it from warm to hot (we go)
Fire, gotta give it all we got (we go)
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Fire
Fire!
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
What's goin' on, Texas?
Are you ready to
catch a fire tonight?
Hoo-a-hoo, dum dum down
Here come that boy from Tennessee town
Hoo-a-hoo, Jamaica bound
Here come that boy boy boy...
Even if I'm christian as a way to go
I'm confessin' it with my mouth
just to make it flow
Then I'm feeling the Holy Spirit
From mi head to mi toe
Then he fillin' up mi cup
'till mi overflow, and go
- Catch a fire, let it burn within now
- Come on!
- Catch a fire, Let it burn for Him
- Get up!
Whoopsi-daisy, call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that
Call me crazy
Whoopsi-daisy
Come, we gonna catch that