Yo, this goes out to anyone listening
Out, out, out the stereo system
Ladies and gentleman, DJ Maj
- What you got?
- I've been around the way
I've been around the block
I got the keys to the city
if the gates are locked
And a freak like me
ain't 'bout to stop
I got a hand full of dreams
and a heart full of God
Everywhere we go
they wonder where we're from
Well, its diverse city,
ya'll welcome to come
It sits high in the hills,
you can see it for days
And even if you can't
you can hear our praise
We go...
boom, shack, boom-boom to clack
'Cause we're
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Here to rep the most high with this one
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
'Cause we rock for sure in stereo
Boomin' out your stereo
If you're looking to slide,
come slide with us
And if you're looking for a
ride, it's a big old bus
We got black folk, white folk
and Middle East
Mexican, Filipino, Jesus Freaks
Got a Haitian Princess, an Aussie Mate
East Coast, Midwest
to left side of the states
And when the bus rolls,
it's out the dirty south
Tennessee and we keepin' it
good and loud
We go...
Boom, shack, boom-boom to clack
'Cause we're
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Here to rep the most high with this one
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out your stereo
Welcome to
the Portable Sounds store y'all
- Tell'em Toby
- I got Portable Sounds to lift me up
Portable Sounds to take me higher
Portable Sounds to lift me up
So don't even try to get in my head
I got portable sounds to lift me up
Portable Sounds to take me higher
Portable Sounds to lift me up
- So don't even try to get in my head
- Take it up!
We got Portable Sounds to lift us up
Portable Sounds to take us higher
Portable Sounds to lift us up
- Portable Sounds to take us higher
- Shonlock!
Boom, shaka-laka,
I gotta pop it and lock it
And lockin' and poppin', I'm thinkin' they
stoppin', 'bout to say somethin'
- Boom!
- Let me check the technique
I speak life from riddle
with a flow that's unique
- We go boom!
- They bite every word that I utter
So tasty, tantalizing,
make room, mister runner
Here we go, check out
the scenario and the flow
Got 'em bangin'
Boomin' out the stereo, stereo!
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Here to rep the most high with this one
Boomin' out the stereo system
This goes out to anyone listening
Boomin' out your stereo
Yeah, oh, oh
We're boomin' the truth
out the speakers, yo!
Boomin' out the stereo